baycongroup.com 2004-06-03

# Privacy Policy

****BayCon Group Privacy Policy****

We at BayCon Group believe that your privacy is very important.  We understand that you are trusting us to act in a responsible manner when you provide us with personal information.  Your trust is very important to us. The information you provide will only be used to help us provide you with better service.

**Your Privacy**  
We never provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals. We may, however, use the contents of e-mail messages for promotional purposes. If we use your e-mail message for promotional purposes, you will only be identified by your first name or your initials.

BayCon Group frequently receives questions from students. If you e-mail us a question, we may post your question and our answer in a forum. Again, you will only be identified by your first name or your initials.

**What personal information do we collect?**  
When you visit our Web site and access information you remain anonymous. The only personal information we have is the information your choose to provide us.

**What statistical information do we collect?**  
BayCon Group collects the following statistical information: IP address, accesses, and referring URL.

**Use of Cookies**  
BayCon Group does not use cookies.  However, some of the agencies that serve ads to our our site may use cookies. A list of these agencies and links to their site is provided on this page. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy policy of each agency.

**Advertising on Our Site**  
BayCon Group works with third party agencies that serve ads to our site. If you are concerned about privacy, we strongly encourage you to review the privacy policy of each agency. 

[BURST! Media, LLC   
](http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp)[Advertising.com](http://www.advertising.com/privacy/index.html)[  
](http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp)[Engage Technologies Inc.](http://www.engage.com/privacy/)[  
](http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp)[Clear Blue Media](http://www.clearbluemedia.com/)

**Site Survey  
**A link to a Site Survey can be found on our home page. We encourage you to complete the survey. The information provided in the survey is not being collected by or on behalf of BayCon Group. This information is being collected by BURST! Media, LLC for advertising purposes. BayCon Group is contractually obligated to post this survey. 

**Questions and Comments**  
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, please contact us at [privacy@baycongroup.com](mailto:privacy@baycongroup.com)

\- - - -

BayCon Group works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Engage Media manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to [http://www.engage.com/privacy.](http://www.engage.com/privacy/)

Copyright © 1999 - 2000 BayCon Group, Inc. All rights reserved
